I eat a lot of ice cream and here's how
I do it without losing track of my
fitness goals. I use the Ninja Creamy to
make low calorie high protein ice cream
every night and it's still delicious.
Here are the five I made this week.
Started off strong with the Cosmic
Brownie ice cream. This was a dark
brownie batter base with the little
sprinkles mixed in. Then I did a s'mores
ice cream. This was a graham cracker
base with marshmallows, graham crackers,
and chocolate mixed in. Then I made a
Tonight ice cream. This was delicious.
Chocolate base with cookie dough. Peanut
butter cookie dough and Oreo mixed
in. Then I decided to mix in a Bearbells
into things. The best protein bar I've
ever tried. This was a peanut butter
base with a salted caramel peanut
Bearbells mixed in. So, a ton of
protein. That one was a little high in
the calories, so I decided to go low for
this one. The cake batter frosty. Super
simple recipe. Just pretty much cake
batter extract and a vanilla base. And
that's all for the week.